whats-on-netflix.com 2019-07-14

# Privacy Policy - What's on Netflix

What’s on Netflix (POSTERITY INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY LTD) is committed to safeguarding your privacy. Contact us at if you have any questions or problems regarding the use of your Personal Data and we will gladly assist you.

By using this site or/and our services, you consent to the Processing of your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Table of Contents

  1. Definitions used in this Policy
  2. Data protection principles we follow
  3. What rights do you have regarding your Personal Data
  4. What Personal Data we gather about you
  5. How we use your Personal Data
  6. Who else has access to your Personal Data
  7. How we secure your data
  8. Information about cookies
  9. Contact information

 **Personal Data**  – any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.  
**Processing**  – any operation or set of operations which is performed on Personal Data or on sets of Personal Data.  
**Data subject**  – a natural person whose Personal Data is being Processed.  
**Child** – a natural person under 16 years of age.  
**We/us** (either capitalized or not) –

We promise to follow the following data protection principles:

  * Processing is lawful, fair, transparent. Our Processing activities have lawful grounds. We always consider your rights before Processing Personal Data. We will provide you information regarding Processing upon request.
  * Processing is limited to the purpose. Our Processing activities fit the purpose for which Personal Data was gathered.
  * Processing is done with minimal data. We only gather and Process the minimal amount of Personal Data required for any purpose.
  * Processing is limited with a time period. We will not store your personal data for longer than needed.
  * We will do our best to ensure the accuracy of data.
  * We will do our best to ensure the integrity and confidentiality of data.

The Data Subject has the following rights:

  1. Right to information – meaning you have to right to know whether your Personal Data is being processed; what data is gathered, from where it is obtained and why and by whom it is processed.
  2. Right to access – meaning you have the right to access the data collected from/about you. This includes your right to request and obtain a copy of your Personal Data gathered.
  3. Right to rectification – meaning you have the right to request rectification or erasure of your Personal Data that is inaccurate or incomplete.
  4. Right to erasure – meaning in certain circumstances you can request for your Personal Data to be erased from our records.
  5. Right to restrict processing – meaning where certain conditions apply, you have the right to restrict the Processing of your Personal Data.
  6. Right to object to processing – meaning in certain cases you have the right to object to Processing of your Personal Data, for example in the case of direct marketing.
  7. Right to object to automated Processing – meaning you have the right to object to automated Processing, including profiling; and not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated Processing. This right you can exercise whenever there is an outcome of the profiling that produces legal effects concerning or significantly affecting you.
  8. Right to data portability – you have the right to obtain your Personal Data in a machine-readable format or if it is feasible, as a direct transfer from one Processor to another.
  9. Right to lodge a complaint – in the event that we refuse your request under the Rights of Access, we will provide you with a reason as to why. If you are not satisfied with the way your request has been handled please contact us.
  10. Right for the help of supervisory authority – meaning you have the right for the help of a supervisory authority and the right for other legal remedies such as claiming damages.
  11. Right to withdraw consent – you have the right withdraw any given consent for Processing of your Personal Data.

 **Information you have provided us with**  
This might be your e-mail address, name, billing address, home address etc – mainly information that is necessary for delivering you a product/service or to enhance your customer experience with us. We save the information you provide us with in order for you to comment or perform other activities on the website. This information includes, for example, your name and e-mail address.

 **Information automatically collected about you**  
This includes information that is automatically stored by cookies and other session tools. For example, your shopping cart information, your IP address, your shopping history (if there is any) etc. This information is used to improve your customer experience. When you use our services or look at the contents of our website, your activities may be logged.

 **Information from our partners**  
We gather information from our trusted partners with confirmation that they have legal grounds to share that information with us. This is either information you have provided them directly with or that they have gathered about you on other legal grounds. See the list of our partners here.

We use your Personal Data in order to:

  * to receive regular newsletters or curated newsletters
  * send push notifications to desktop and mobile devices
  * enhance your customer experience;
  * fulfil an obligation under law or contract;

We use your Personal Data on legitimate grounds and/or with your Consent.

On the grounds of entering into a contract or fulfilling contractual obligations, we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:

  * to identify you;
  * to promote our content

On the ground of legitimate interest, we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:

  * to administer and analyse our readership base (site activity) in order to improve the quality, variety, and availability of services offered/provided;

With your consent we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:

  * to send you newsletters or notifications regarding content on our website.
  * for other purposes we have asked your consent for;

We Process your Personal Data in order to fulfil obligation rising from law and/or use your Personal Data for options provided by law. We reserve the right to anonymise Personal Data gathered and to use any such data. We will use data outside the scope of this Policy only when it is anonymised.

We might process your Personal Data for additional purposes that are not mentioned here, but are compatible with the original purpose for which the data was gathered. To do this, we will ensure that:

  * the link between purposes, context and nature of Personal Data is suitable for further Processing;
  * the further Processing would not harm your interests and
  * there would be appropriate safeguard for Processing.

We will inform you of any further Processing and purposes.

We do not share your Personal Data with strangers. Personal Data about you is in some cases provided to our trusted partners in order to either make providing the service to you possible or to enhance your customer experience. We share your data with:

 **Our processing partners:**

  *  **GRV Media**

 **Connected third parties:**

### Advertising

This type of service allows User Data to be utilized for advertising communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on this Website, possibly based on User interests.  
This does not mean that all Personal Data are used for this purpose. Information and conditions of use are shown below.  
Some of the services listed below may use Cookies to identify Users or they may use the behavioral retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the User’s interests and behavior, including those detected outside this Website. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services.  
In addition to any opt out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

#### DoubleClick for Publishers (Google Inc.)

DoubleClick for Publishers is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. that allows the Owner to run advertising campaigns in conjunction with external advertising networks that the Owner, unless otherwise specified in this document, has no direct relationship with. In order to opt out from being tracked by various advertising networks, Users may make use of [Youronlinechoices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). In order to understand Google’s use of data, consult [Google’s partner policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).  
This service uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of this Website and User behavior concerning ads, products and services offered.  
Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en](https://myaccount.google.com/not-supported).

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

#### Criteo (Criteo SA)

Criteo is an advertising service provided by Criteo SA.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: France – [Privacy Policy](https://www.criteo.com/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.criteo.com/privacy/).

#### AppNexus (AppNexus Inc.)

AppNexus is an advertising service provided by AppNexus Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.appnexus.com/platform-privacy-policy) – [Opt out](https://www.appnexus.com/platform-privacy-policy#choices).

#### RhythmOne (Burst Media Corporation)

RhythmOne is an advertising service provided by RhythmOne, LLC.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.rhythmone.com/privacy-policy) – [Opt out](https://www.rhythmone.com/opt-out).

#### Rubicon Project (The Rubicon Project, Inc.)

Rubicon Project is an advertising service provided by The Rubicon Project, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

#### Index Exchange (Index Exchange)

Index Exchange is an advertising service provided by Index Exchange.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/) – [Opt Out](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/).

#### Sovrn (Sovrn Holdings, Inc)

Sovrn is an advertising service provided by Sovrn Holdings, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.sovrn.com/sovrn-legal-policies/) – [Opt Out](https://info.evidon.com/pub_info/2672?v=1&nt=0&nw=false).

#### bRealTime (EMX Digital LLC)

bRealTime is an advertising service provided by EMX Digital LLC (a subsidiary of Engine Media LLC).

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.brealtime.com/privacy-policy/) – [Opt Out](http://optout.aboutads.info/?lang=EN&c=2#!/).

#### Playground XYZ (Playground XYZ Holdings Pty Ltd.)

Playground XYZ is an advertising service provided by Playground XYZ Holdings Pty Ltd.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: Australia – [Privacy Policy](https://playground.xyz/privacy/privacy-policy.pdf) – Opt Out.

#### GumGum (GumGum, Inc.)

GumGum is an advertising service provided by GumGum, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://gumgum.com/privacy-policy) – [Opt Out](https://gumgum.com/opt-out).

#### JustPremium (JustPremium BV)

JustPremium is an advertising service provided by JustPremium BV

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: Netherlands – Privacy Policy – Opt Out.

#### District M (District M, Inc.)

District M is an advertising service provided by District M, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://districtm.net/en/page/data-and-privacy-policy/) – [Opt Out](https://cdn.districtm.ca/optout.html).

#### 152 Media (152 Media, LLC.)

152 Media is an advertising service provided by 152 Media, LLC.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.152media.com/privacy.html) – [Opt Out](https://app.onetrust.com/app/#/webform/8a17cf9b-19c4-4f99-a32d-4dd3b0f21c93).

#### Ad You Like (Ad You Like.)

Ad You Like is an advertising service provided by Ad You Like

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.adyoulike.com/privacy_policy.php) – Opt Out.

#### Sonobi (Sonobi, Inc.)

Sonobi is an advertising service provided by Sonobi, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://sonobi.com/privacy-policy/) – [Opt Out](https://sonobi.com/opt-out/).

We only work with Processing partners who are able to ensure adequate level of protection to your Personal Data. We disclose your Personal Data to third parties or public officials when we are legally obliged to do so. We might disclose your Personal Data to third parties if you have consented to it or if there are other legal grounds for it.

## Akismet

We collect information about visitors who comment on Sites that use our Akismet anti-spam service. The information we collect depends on how the User sets up Akismet for the Site, but typically includes the commenter’s IP address, user agent, referrer, and Site URL (along with other information directly provided by the commenter such as their name, username, email address, and the comment itself).

We do our best to keep your Personal Data safe.  We use safe protocols for communication and transferring data (such as HTTPS). We use anonymising and pseudonymising where suitable. We monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks. ** **

Even though we try our best we can not guarantee the security of information. However, we promise to notify suitable authorities of data breaches. We will also notify you if there is a threat to your rights or interests. We will do everything we reasonably can to prevent security breaches and to assist authorities should any breaches occur.

If you have an account with us, note that you have to keep your username and password secret.

### Children

We do not intend to collect or knowingly collect information from children. We do not target children with our services.

We use cookies and/or similar technologies to analyse customer behaviour, administer the website, track users’ movements, and to collect information about users. This is done in order to personalise and enhance your experience with us.

A cookie is a tiny text file stored on your computer. Cookies store information that is used to help make sites work. Only we can access the cookies created by our website. You can control your cookies at the browser level. Choosing to disable cookies may hinder your use of certain functions.

 **We use cookies for the following purposes:**

  * Necessary cookies – these cookies are required for you to be able to use some important features on our website, such as logging in. These cookies don’t collect any personal information.
  * Functionality cookies – these cookies provide functionality that makes using our service more convenient and makes providing more personalised features possible. For example, they might remember your name and e-mail in comment forms so you don’t have to re-enter this information next time when commenting.
  * Analytics cookies – these cookies are used to track the use and performance of our website and services
  * Advertising cookies – these cookies are used to deliver advertisements that are relevant to you and to your interests. In addition, they are used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement. They are usually placed to the website by advertising networks with the website operator’s permission. These cookies remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organisations such as advertisers. Often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organisation.

You can remove cookies stored in your computer via your browser settings. Alternatively, you can control some 3rd party cookies by using a privacy enhancement platform such as optout.aboutads.info or [youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). For more information about cookies, visit [allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

We use Google Analytics to measure traffic on our website. Google has their own Privacy Policy which you can review [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245). If you’d like to opt out of tracking by Google Analytics, visit the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Kasey Moore

[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

+44 (0) 1603 633202

We reserve the right to make change to this Privacy Policy.
